A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
T. Marshall Hahn Records, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr. (Thomas Marshall), 1926-2016
RG 2/11
101 Cubic Feet 101 boxes (3319 folders)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Biographical/Historical Information
Being selected as VPI's eleventh president at the age of 35 made Hahn the youngest man to ever hold the position. During his administration, which began 2 July 1962, VPI became known as "Virginia's Land-Grant University." There was a shift from traditional technically-oriented education to a more comprehensive University-oriented education, with programs being expanded through the doctoral level in many non-science areas. The culmination of this shift and expansion in mission came in 1970 when the Legislature approved a name change reflective of VPI's growth: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University.
Major events of the Hahn administration included abolishment of the VPI-Radford merger, causing a large increase in the number of women students at Tech, and a decision by the Board of Visitors to make participation in the military program optional, which resulted in a decline in Corps of Cadets membership but an increase in male Virginians choosing to attend the University. There were also numerous organizational and academic changes and improvements, including the establishment of a University-wide Research Division and a University-wide Extension Division, both in 1966. Also the physical plant continued to expand during this administration.
Some of the later years of the Hahn administration were marked by student demonstrations and protests, like those which occurred at many university campuses in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
After twelve years in office, Hahn sent a letter to faculty and staff in August 1974 indicating his decision to resign as president, stating that "it is not in the best interest of a university for one person to serve as president for too long a time." In November, William Lavery was named to succeed Hahn, beginning in January 1975.
Scope and Content Information
This collection contains primarily correspondence concerning University matters, including letters to and from alumni, faculty, parents, and students. Correspondence with the Board of Visitors and government officials is also included in the collection. There is material concerning the Alumni Association, budget information, Higher Education Study Commission (1965), University Council, Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, State Council of Higher Education in Virginia, Task Force for Innovative Approaches to Instruction (1973), Consortium for Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia (1973), civil rights, proposal for College of Veterinary Medicine (1974, Box 95, folders 3211-3215), and various University committees and commissions. There is a large amount of material dealing with student protests (1970-71, see Boxes 45-47), including correspondence to and from parents, students, and the general public. The collection also includes copies of many of Hahn's speeches (1961-73), such as "Statement on Need of a College of Veterinary Medicine in Virginia" and "Virginia in the Jet Age."
The collection also contains Hahn's files of the Metropolitan Study Commission that he chaired from 1966 to 1968, including correspondence, minutes, and reports. This commission was created by the 1966 Virginia General Assembly to "make a comprehensive study of metropolitan governmental problems and to undertake to develop solutions to such problems."
There is also material on the Virginia Associated Research Center (VARC), including correspondence, reports, and Governing Committee minutes (1963-67). VARC was an off-campus graduate facility sponsored by Virginia Tech, the College of William and Mary, and the University of Virginia, in cooperation with the Langley Research Center of NASA. It specialized in applied aerospace research and other basic research in related areas.
The University Archives also contains the records of Hahn's inauguration, including correspondence, programs, invitations, some minutes and other documents of the Inauguration Committee and its subcommittees on Local Arrangements, Reception, and Invitations and Programs. There is a notebook (see Box 98, folder 3277b) containing various articles and clippings on college budgets and campus unrest throughout the United States, plus a handwritten copy of a speech entitled "The Role of the Academic Community in Campus Unrest" (Box 101, folder 3319), and a typed paper entitled "Legislation and Appropriations in Other States Relating to Higher Education" that includes handwritten additions. Also in this collection is a bound volume containing photocopies of press clippings from the Conference on Artificial Satellites (12-16 August 196?, Box 101, folder 3277c).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged according to date.
Index Terms
Persons:
Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr. (Thomas Marshall), 1926-2016
Subjects:
Faculty; University Archives; University History; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Women -- History
- Series I, 1962-1965
  - A-miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting Office: Mr. Fred O'Connell, Accountant, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accounting--National Committee on Accounting, E.C.P.D., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions: Dr. P.H. Farrier, Director, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aerospace Engineering Department: J.D. Eades, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture Director of Instruction--Dr. J.T. Harn, Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Education, Vocational Education, Business Education: Prof. H.W. Sanders, Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture Economics, Rural Sociology: Dr. H.M. Lone, Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agricultural Engineering: Professor E.T. Swink, Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agronomy Department: Dr. H. L. Dunton Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association Fund Council, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association Presidents Emergencies Fund, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association-General #1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Association-General #2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association-General #3, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Citations, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Council on Education, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Animal Husbandry Department: Professor G. W. Litton, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Architecture Department: Professor L.J. Currie, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - File on Proposed School of Architecture and Allied Arts: Far. Dr. Newman, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Applications--Positions, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Associations of American Colleges, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Associations of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Association of Land Grant College Centennial, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Athletic Council, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Biology and Nutrition Department: Dr. R.W. Engel, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Streeter Blair Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget Director Mr. L.M. Kuhn, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Budget Matters, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Buildings and Grounds: Mr. Russell Abbitt, Superintendent, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - business administration Department: Dr. H. H. Mitchell, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Business Manager: Mrs. S. K. Cassell, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Calender Commitments, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Chemistry Department: Dr. R. C. Krugs, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Chemical Engineering Department: Dr. F.W. Bull, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - College Calendar, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Civil Engineering Department: Dr. H. M. Marris, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Commandant of Cadets: General M.W. Schewe, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - "Naming Committee, V.P.I. Buildings", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Committee on Naming Buildings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Consulting Work for Faculty, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Community Concert Association, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - D-miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dairy Science Department: Dr. G.C. Graf, Department Head, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Development Program #1: Mr. Earl Fisher, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Development Program #2: Mr. Earl Fisher, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dean L. B. Dietrick #1: Dean of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dean L.B. Dietrick #2: Dean of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dining Hall: Director, Mr. H.P. King, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Dormitories Director: Mr. J.E. Hardy, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Doughtrey, W.H.: Associate Director Extension, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Economic Council Letters, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - English and Foreign Languages: Dr. M.L. Peacock, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Electrical Engineering Department: Professor G.R. Powley, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Engineering Mechanics Department: Professor D.H. Pletta, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Entomology Department: Dr. J.M. Grayson, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Extension--General, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - F--miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Faculty List, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Faculty Committees, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Forestry, Wildlife, and Conservation: Dr. J. F. Hasner, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Fund Raising, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - The Governor of Virginia: The Honorable Albert S. Harrison, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Graphics Department: Professor J.R. Castleman, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Geological Science Department: Dr. B.N. Cooper, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Guidance and Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - History Department: Dr. Archer Jones, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Horticulture Department: Dr. W.P. Judkins, Department Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Inaugural Exercises- April 1963, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Industrial Engineering Department: Professor H.L. Manning, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Invitations-Inauguration, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Invitations--Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, Head, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Home Economics Department: Dr. Laura J. Harper, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Johnston, G. Burke, Dean, Science and General Studies, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Joint Office of Industrial Research, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Legislation, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Library: Mr. Frank Shirk, Acting Director, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Mathematics Department: Dr. J.W. Hatcher, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Mechanical Engineering Department: Professor J. B. Jones, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Military Department: Colonel T. M. Larner, Army; Colonel Ray W. Koontz, Air Force, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Mining Engineering:Dr. J.R. Lucas, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - N-Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - NASA: VARC Langley Field, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Dr. Louis A. Pardue, Vice President and Director of Graduate Studies, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Philosophy and Religion Department: Dr. Newman Grover, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Physics Department: Dr. J. A. Jacobs, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Director of Personnel: Mr. J.W. Garber--Richmond, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Personnel Manager: Mr. E.B. Evans-Blacksburg, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Planning Engineer: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenburg, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Poultry Husbandry Department: Dr. C.E. Howes, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Plant Pathology Department: Dr. S.A. Wingard, Department Head, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Presidents Council, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Presidents Institute, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Publicity Director: Mr. R.H. McNeil, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Purchasing Department: Mr. Nunnally-Richmond; Mr. H.W. Swink-Blacksburg, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Q-Miscellaneous; Questionnaires, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Radford College: President Dr. C.K. Martin, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Registrar: Miss Clarice Slusher, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Requisitions, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Religious Activities: Mr. Paul N. Derring, Director, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Salary Schedules, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Southern Association: Report by October 1, 1962, Session 1961-1962, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Southern Athletic Conference, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Dr. Stuart B. Row, Coordinator in Charge of Branch Institutions, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - State Board of Education, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Statistics Department: Dr. Boyd Harshburger, Department Head (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Student Affairs: January-June, Dr. James W. Dean, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Student Affairs: July-December, Dr. James W. Dean, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Student Housing, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Student Organizations, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Student Letters, Parents, and Friends, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Student Letters, To and From, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Summer Conferences, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Treasurer: Mr. J.F. Boone, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - U-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - U.S. Civil Service, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - V-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Veterinary Science: Dr. D.F. Watson, Department Head, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Virginia State Board of Agriculture: Mr. Park Brinkley, Commissioner, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Academic Vice-Presidency Prospects, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station: Dr. H.N. Young; Dr. W.B. Bell, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association: Mr. F.O. Mosley, Director, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - VPI Education Foundation: Dr. John R. Hutcheson, President, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Executive Secretary: Jas L.W. West, Jr., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Engineering and Architecture: Dean John W. Whittemore, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Accrediting-National Commission on Accrediting, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Alumni Association-General #1, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Alumni Association-General #2, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Alumni Association-General #3, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Alumni Association-Bylaws, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Alumni Office, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Alumni: C. Eugene Rowe, President, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Alumni Association President's Emergency Fund, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Alumni Association Fund Council, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Architecture Department, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and state Universities, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Budget Director: Mr. L.M. Kuhn, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Budget Matters, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Attorney General: The Honorable Robert Y. Button, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Cabins, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - College Calendar, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Awards Committee, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Faculty Committees, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Community Concert Association, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Computer Recommendations-I.B.M., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Development, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Development Program, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - R. Craig Fabian, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - General Electric Salem, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Governor of Virginia: the Honorable Albertis S. Harrison, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Guidance and Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, Department Head, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, President, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Home Economics: Dr. Laura J. Harper, Department Head, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Inaugural Exercises, April, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Kennedy, J.F., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Legislation, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Library Annual Report: Mr. Frank Shirk, Acting Director, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Metallurgical Engineering, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Mining-Engineering, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - NASA, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Radford College: Dr. C. K. Martin, President, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Dr. Stuart B. Row, Coordinator in Charge of Branch Institutions, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Placement, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Presidents Council, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Dr. Lewis A. Pardue, Vice President and Director of Graduate Studies, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Director of Personnel: Mr. J.W. Garber-Richmond, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Registrar: Miss Clarice Slusher, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Religious Activities: Mr. Paul M. Deering, Director, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Research Park, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Scholarships, Fellowships and Loans, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Southern Athletic Conference, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - State Board of Education, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Student Affairs- January through June: Dr. James W. Dean, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Tech Festival, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Vice President: Dr. Warren W. Brandt, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - VPI Agricultural Publications, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association: Mr. F.O. Mosley, Director, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Visiting Scholars Program, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - YMCA: Mr. A.L. Payne, Secretary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Academic Council, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Accrediting-National Commission on Accrediting- E.C.P.D., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Alumni President: Mr. C. Eugene Rowe, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Alumni Secretary: Mr. M.L. Oliver, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Annual Reports, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 223a)
  - Appalachian Institute- Mr. William R. Ewald, Jr., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Association Land- Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Division of Budget: Mr. L.M. Kuhn, Director, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Budget Matters, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Mr. J.R. Abbitt, Director, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Business Manager: Mr. S.K. Cassell, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Cabins, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Community Colleges: Dr. S.B. Row, Coordinator, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Construction Science Institute, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Corps, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Development and Public Relations: Mr. R.C. Fabian, Director, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Development Council #1, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Development Council #2, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Faculty Committees, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Ford Foundation, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Football, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Fred Baker, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Governor of Virginia: The Honorable Albertis S. Harrison, Jr., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Mr. J. Ambler Johnston, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Legislation, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Letters-Complaints from file-Presidents Office, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Medical Research Laboratory, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Mottley, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Naming Buildings, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - NASA, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - J.M.H. New Products, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Jack Newman, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., Personal, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Personnel-Blacksburg: Mr. E.B. Evans, Director, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Personnel- Richmond: Mr. J.W. Garber, Director, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Physics Department: Dr. James A. Jacobs, Department Head, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Position Analysis- Biennium #1, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 261a)
  - Position Analysis- Biennium #2, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 261b)
  - Presidents Council, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Radford College: Dr. C.K. Martin, President, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Grants, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Southern Conference, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - State Board of Education, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - State Council of Higher Education: Dr. William Hugh McFarlane, Director, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Tech Festival, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Technical Education Department, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Tektronix Foundation, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Treasurer, Mr. J.F. Boone, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - University Research, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - V.A.R.C. #1, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - V.A.R.C. #2, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - V.A.R.C. #3, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - V.A.R.C. Governing Committee, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - V.A.R.C. Minutes, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - VPI Education Foundation, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 287)